A weekend retreat... where no one returns.
Backwoods is a horror, thriller, tv movie film directed by Martin Jay Weiss.
A group of friends embark on a camping trip for a ten-year high school reunion.
Their celebration soon turns into a battle for survival when they realize that
the locals, who are not what they seem, are hunting them down.
Lee, played by Haylie Duff.
Adam, played by Ryan Merriman.
Ricks, played by Mark Rolston.
Perry Walters, played by Danny Nucci.
Chris Basso, played by Troy Winbush.
Mother Ruth, played by Deborah Van Valkenburgh.
Backwoods is a 2008 American horror television film directed by
Marty Weiss and starring Ryan Merriman & Haylie Duff.
It premiered on June 8, 2008 on Spike TV.
The film explores themes of suicide, fbi, camping, north carolina, redneck.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking and intense.